That almost dreams are looking at a cut towards thousand
but Goldman Sachs report from here this
entry tree such a target of ₹100 is to be heard
that is the meeting of the set I have
given no 8585 Raigarh should get rid of serial 7865
and the rating of perfume set and so by
the way profitability Boss stock has been limited by
JP Morgan formed around seven thousand
rupees. New Trans Maintain has an
empty exit poll at the bottom. Otherwise if you
look at its range then it can be
seen stagnating somewhere between 7000 to nine thousand. The
number is much better than Salman. It was
also talked about the reduction of the base
that this time it has come for the national company
and along with this, by the time the company's net
starch comes to 2050, then this company's
situation is also going to change a lot. The
record brings a little favorable gift
after falling down, so you
can buy more here. The second set in Bajaj Auto has
around 47 and
usage rating from Sample by Morgan Stanley is overweight.  He has
kept himself and 4550 for
decorating it, a call has been given to him from the department
that MP ₹4000 Tiger Shroff is selling like Citi, the
target is ₹3000
but this cancer is also a buy here and
Tiger is seen to be around ₹4000,
he believes that the situation of the company has
definitely gone down a bit,
like water scooter has been seen, work on TV and
hybrid in the company has been
made for this, apart from that, in the
coming time, quantity, cost,
low pressure will remain within the sponsors, you can
see more dominance and they are
going to word motorcycle product mix
and domestic demand, these are the stands which will
definitely be monitored, so
maintain the budget from here also, Majorganj institutional keeps
coming around ₹4000, third Bharti Airtel, this is
not a sarcasm here but the commentary
is quite positive, from Goldman Sachs as well as from
Citi, he said that the
talks of terrific  The terrific impact
that
comes on the prepaid customers is important
and one very good thing is that
if this is clarified across pan
India then three
to six percent incremental wireless
revenue and son can be seen,
Citi also did not say that if the
situation of the total post segment improves then from
there also we are
seeing growth of around one percent
and the Revenue Secretary's mission is
modern, five percent of the company's
subscribers everywhere contribute
to PUPs and apart from that, the remote repeat from mobile to
cyber contributes around 12%, so we are considering it
a big nutritious find for the company, there should be
different interaction in the target, but I think
that when the situation is bad, there is difficulty in revenue, so we have
seen it, so
here you can see that it is good that
he said that there is definitely a Bhanot
in the scooter, that is why they have
definitely revised the target but it is not very big.
15 The first target was ₹70, it has been revised and
tested for around ₹100
and there is a rating of out for site. They believe
that the situation in the second half will be
seen to be a little better in
comparison to this quarter. On the other hand, in the
fourth quarter guest lectures, we will
see more special underwriting
and around ₹500. Limited
got to learn their numbers, but yes, they feel that the
overall situation will get better around 1423 on words. The
replacement for f22 has definitely been removed. Cars page
around five percent, but for refer 2334,
only around three to five percent. We are
seeing a lot of damage in the playlist withdrawal,
but we are still
targeting Bijnor of from the rest on the site.
Ajay ko jhal jhal jhal